<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 on Zuhui Wang&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://wzhings.github.io/publication_types/2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 on Zuhui Wang&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} Zuhui Wang</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wzhings.github.io/publication_types/2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Medical Misinformation on Social Media Using Multimodal Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://wzhings.github.io/publication/journals/antivaccine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wzhings.github.io/publication/journals/antivaccine/</guid>
      <description>Abstract In 2019, outbreaks of vaccine-preventable diseases reached the highest number in the US since 1992. Medical misinformation, such as antivaccine content propagating through social media, is associated with increases in vaccine delay and refusal. Our overall goal is to develop an automatic detector for antivaccine messages to counteract the negative impact that antivaccine messages have on the public health. Very few extant detection systems have considered multimodality of social media posts (images, texts, and hashtags), and instead focus on textual components, despite the rapid growth of photo-sharing applications (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effects of visual congruence on increasing consumers’ brand engagement: An empirical investigation of influencer marketing on instagram using deep-learning algorithms for automatic image classification</title>
      <link>https://wzhings.github.io/publication/journals/visualcong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wzhings.github.io/publication/journals/visualcong/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Influencers are non-celebrity individuals who gain popularity on social media by posting visually attractive content (e.g., photos and videos) and by interacting with other users (i.e., Followers) to create a sense of authenticity and friendship. Brands partner with Influencers to garner engagement from their target consumers in a new marketing strategy known as “Influencer marketing.” Nonetheless, the theoretical underpinnings of such remains unknown. We suggest a new conceptual framework of “Visual-Congruence-induced Social Influence (VCSI),” which contextualizes the Similarity-Attraction Model in the Social Influence literature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>